burnworld.com 2010-06-04

# Burnworld - Privacy Policy

| 

|  | **Privacy Statement for BurnWorld.COM**

BurnWorld has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: BurnWorld.com.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Click Here.

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Just Email [rob @burnworld.com](mailto:rob%20@burnworld.com)

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [Rob](mailto:rob%20@burnworld.com)

| This policy will let you know:  
---  

  1. [What information is collected from you](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#what);
  2. [What cookies are and how they are used](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#cookies); 
  3. [How your information is used](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#how); 
  4. [Who is collecting your information](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#who); 
  5. [With whom your information may be shared](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#share); 
  6. [The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#security);
  7. [The Opt-in/Opt-out policy](http://www.burnworld.com/privacy.htm#opt);

**What information does BurnWorld.com collect from me?**  
BurnWorld.com collects information from a variety of web pages. We collect your contact information so that we can reply to your contact requests.  
   
**What are cookies and how does BurnWorld.com use them?**  
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, BurnWorld.com use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. All sites on BurnWorld.com where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. 

Generally, we use cookies to: 

  1. Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. This cookie is set when you register or "Sign In" and is modified when you "Sign Out" of our services.
  2. Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing BurnWorld.com is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by a registered user versus by an unregistered user, and to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior.
  3. Assist merchants affiliated with BurnWorld.com to track visits to and business at their stores, and to process the items in your shopping basket. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called "click stream" or "click trail" and may also describe which pages you have seen in each merchant's store.
  4. Measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of BurnWorld.com you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another so that we can make each new experience on BurnWorld.com a better one. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites.

Advertising networks that serve ads onto BurnWorld.com may also use their own cookies. 

BurnWorld.com also collects IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. In addition, BurnWorld.com Mail includes IP addresses in outgoing mail message headers.  

**How does BurnWorld.com use my information?**  
BurnWorld.com's primary goal in collecting information is to provide you, the user, with comparative affiliate software information. This information is available free of charge and no compensation is expected. 

Another goal of BurnWorld.com is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our network of sites. This includes personalization services, interactive communications, online shopping and many other types of services, most of which are completely free to you. In order to provide services free of charge, we may display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, BurnWorld.com is able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content, and hence better service to you.  

**Who is collecting information?**  
When you are on the BurnWorld.com site and are asked for information, you are providing that information to BurnWorld.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise.  
   
****  
If you are requesting assistance, demos, or brochures, your contact information may be shared with the owner of the relevant affiliate software. For example, some BurnWorld.com services are offered in conjunction with a partner company. This information is shared with the partner company so that they may provide you with the affiliate software demo, brochures and/or an online consultation.  
   
**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**  
As a global company BurnWorld.com has users all over the world. When you give BurnWorld.com personal information, that information may be sent electronically to servers outside of the country where you originally entered the information, such as to the United States or other countries. In addition, that information may be used, stored and processed outside of the country where you entered that information. Whenever BurnWorld.com handles personal information as described above, regardless of where this occurs, BurnWorld.com takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, BurnWorld.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online.  
  
**How can I opt-out of your newsletters and registration?**  
All our newsletters are double-optin. This means that you first requested to get email from us and then your request and email address has been verified by you. 

In every scheduled email we send, there is an option to opt-out of our regular newsletter.

Some emails are non-scheduled such as site/user news for registered users or direct communications. Registered users can opt-out of any further user communications by deactivating their account. To stop receiving personal/business related direct emails just reply to the sender.  
  
| 

* * *

|  | BurnWorld.com is an independent product reviewer and is not associated with any company that is listed on our sites. On occasion we will receive free copies of software for testing & reviewing. We also receive compensation for certain products that are listed on our site. Because of this we would like to mention that this does not alter what we recommend. We take pride in only listing hardware & software that we feel is the best in class and what we would consider a 'safe buy'.  
---|---  

| 

* * *

* * *

|
